# YUMENG\_LI

My Portfolio Website: <a href="https://yumelol.github.io/my-portfolio/">https://yumelol.github.io/my-portfolio/</a>

GitHub:

https://github.com/YumeLoL

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/yumeng-li-7b0993184/

Phone:

0420859366

Email:

yumeee.lol@gmail.com

## **Technical Skills**

## **Programming Languages:**

HTML, CSS, Javascript (basic) Java, C++.

#### Platform:

WordPress

## **Design Tools:**

Adobe XD, Adobe AI, Adobe PS

#### **Management System:**

ERP System, PDM System, JIRA Ticketing System, and Smokeball.

## **Operating System:**

Windows XP/7/10.

#### **Computer Software:**

Microsoft Office Suite (Excel, Word, Power Point), Office 365.

## **Spoken Languages:**

Bilingual fluency (written, read and spoken) in English and Mandarin.

# **Career Objective**

I am a web developer with excellent experience with web design and development. Have knowledge of HTML/CSS/JavaScript. I am passionate about creating clean & user-friendly websites. I extremely enjoy the process of developing a website and I have a strong willingness to learn new things to develop cool stuff.

# **Employment**



## **Mustard Seed Lawyers**

Box Hill, Melbourne

Aug 2019 - Present

# Assistant(part-time)

- # Providing administrative support, including data entry, and client data management.
- # Drafting correspondence and document management.
- # Maintain records and report on the status of matters.
- # Preparation of forms, distribution, and filing.
- # Attend to general office requirements.
- # Undertake general administrative works and file management using Smokeball.
- # Answered and referred inquiries via phone calls or emails.
- # Provided basic ICT support and maintenance including installation, configuration, and update.
- # Set up hardware and software for new employees.



May 2020 - August 2020

## WordPress Developer (Intern)

- # Management of the digital content via the website from draft, review to publishing.
- # Design and develop webpages on WordPress weekly.
- # Assist in and managing client's enquires via Facebook Business page.
- # Basic troubleshooting with other employees around software function, provide IT support.
- # Work with stakeholders to create novel solutions to problems.
- # Prepare the Administrative Documents.

## **Top Skills**

- Web Design and Development
- **Business Analysis**
- WordPress Design
- **Technical Support**

## **Certifications**

Google Analytics Individual Qualification



Mar 2019 – Jun 2019

## IT Business Analyst (Intern)

# Liaised between the IT department and clients.

# Gathered and evaluated clients' business needs, extracted clients' requirements and documented the business' required conditions and capabilities.

# Transformed clients' requirements into User Stories and Acceptance Criteria.

# Wrote clear requirements and created process diagrams to support the business needs, including Capability Matrix and workflow.

# Assigned, reported and escalates bugs, defects, and requests in the JIRA.

# Monitored the solution developed will meet the business requirements.

# Regularly reported to stakeholders.

# Performed manual testing # Created and maintained training materials, provided support and training for clients.

# Created and edited User Manual.

## Education

## **Performance Education**

Jun 2019 - Sep 2020

Professional Year, Information Technology

### **Master of Information Technology**

Jul 2017 – Jul 2019

Central Queensland University, Melbourne, Australia

### **Bachelor of Computer Science and Technology**

Jul 2010 - Jul 2014

Jilin Business and Technology College, Changchun, China

#### Reference

Reference can be provided upon request